

52, 11th Main Road
Banashankari Stage II
Bengaluru, INDIA 560070
▼ WHC9+8C BSK

- 🖄 varungupta3009@gmail.com
- **&** +91 97398 56528
- 🙏 varungupta3009

# Experience



### **Penetration Tester**

Center for Information Security, Forensics and Cyber Resilience May 2020 – Present (4 mos)



### Student Lead in Network Security and Web Development

Developer Student Clubs • PES University Jan 2019 – Present (1 yr 8 mos)



### **Software Engineer**

Mindtree

Jul 2019 - Feb 2020 (8 mos)

## Education



#### PES University

Bachelor of Technology, Computer Science & Engineering 2017 – 2021



#### R. V. PU College

Pre-University, Affiliated to NCERT, New Delhi, Computer Science 2015 – 2017



## Carmel School, Padmanabhanagar

ICSE, New Delhi — SSLC, Karnataka 2002 – 2015

## **Publications & Awards**

Software Implementation of an Automatic Movable Road Barrier IEEE, October 2019, ISBN: 978-1-7281-1576-4

Prof. C N R Rao Merit Scholarship

PES University, November 2019

## Licenses and Certifications

**Associate Cloud Engineer** 

Google, August 2020

# Languages

English Hindi Kannada

## **Hobbies**

■ Reading

(A) Gaming

🔀 Virtual Aviation

ء	N 4	: .
سح	IVI	usic

# Knowledge and Skills

Python 3
Experience
Skill
JavaScript -
Experience Skill
C/C++
Experience Skill
Java, C#, Go Experience
Skill
Frontend Design and Development
Experience
Skill
Full-Stack Web Development
Experience
Skill
Angular (TS), React (JS/TS)
Experience
Skill
WordPress, CMS
Experience
Skill
Adobe Photoshop & Illustrator
Experience
Skill
Adobe After Effects and Premiere Pro
Experience
2,001,01100
Skill
Skill
Skill  Blender, Pixar Renderman
Skill  Blender, Pixar Renderman  Experience Skill
Skill  Blender, Pixar Renderman  Experience

### About me

I am a programmer and experienced web-developer, fluent in Python, C++, C#, Go with over 9 years of experience in Python and C++, and moderately versed in 7 other languages. I am a polymath and love to explore and try new technologies and fiddling with anything related to computer. I am also a graphics designer and a hobbyist hacker.

I recommend checking out my LinkedIn Profile for real-time accurate information and to stay updated on any changes.

